# **Derek Pacula**

### Full Stack Web Developer

Full Stack Web developer with 5+ years of experience. Co-Lead development of two major start-to-finsh projects utilizing modern web tech including Vue, Angular, Node.JS, and AWS. Responsible for demoing products to clients and boards of clients

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Full Stack Web Developer with more than 5 years of experience in Web Development. Extensive knowledge in current technology stacks and leading proects.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **JUNE 2016 - CURRENT**

## Full Stack Web Developer

Telecos

Developing custom web applications including .NET, C# and serverless web applications using Javascript, Angular, Vue, Node.JS and AWS technologies

Leading product demos to clients and board members

Lead on-site client meetings to understand and articulate wants and desires

Maintaining and developing both new and existing applications

Responsible for translating business requirements into high quality technical designs and working software

Developing wireframes and task flows based on user needs and translating these requirements to create create intuitive, user-friendly software

#### **MAY 2012 - JUNE 2016**

#### Mobile Implementations Analyst

Fiserv

Writing requirements for software development to authorization application

Using, configuring, and modifying third party authorization simulators

Creating detailed, client-facing test scripts for sanctioned, department-wide use  $\,$ 

Application Maintenance

# **SKILLS**

ANGULAR, VUE	UI / UX DESIGN
JAVASCRIPT, NODE.JS	MYSQL, MICROSOFT SQL SERVER
AWS	.NET MVC

# EMPLOYEE SKILLS AND CAREER ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Communication and understanding client requirements

AWS Certified DevOps Professional

Training and mentoring new developers

Two-time employee of the quarter winner at Jelecos

Member of Jelecos Cloud Center of Excellence, an exclusive leadership group

#### **EDUCATION**

AUGUST 2011 -DECMBER 2015

# Bachelor's of Computer Science

University of Nebraska Omaha